oewheelsllc.com 2009-06-04

# Infopia - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

## Transact and Infopia Inc. Online Privacy   
and Security Policies

Infopia values the relationship it has with customers and website visitors, and is committed to responsible information-handling practices. Infopia takes the privacy of customers very seriously and wants you to feel comfortable whenever you visit the website, access online services, or participate in additional online offerings from Infopia.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding submitting your information online, please don't hesitate to contact Infopia. 

Infopia, Inc.  
56 East Broadway, 4th Floor  
Salt Lake City, Utah 84111  
888-337-6352  

### Infopia and Transact Privacy Principles

Infopia's approach to responsible information handling is founded on the basis of the Fair Information Practices, the cornerstone of which is providing notice of information practices and other privacy aspects in order to allow individuals to make informed decisions regarding personally identifiable information. Furthermore, Infopia has adopted leading industry practices as set forth by online privacy standards groups.

Infopia provides you notice of information practices. Infopia offers you choices regarding how personally identifiable information you provide may be used. Infopia protects personally identifiable information. Infopia provides you with means of contact for information practices and other privacy aspects. 

  * Infopia notifies you of information practices. When you visit the website, information may be requested of you in order for you to participate more fully in online offerings and services. When Infopia collects information from you, Infopia will let you know what is being collected, how it is collected, for what purpose(s) it is collected and to whom it may be disclosed. Infopia also identifies the information that is necessary to fulfill your request. Whenever Infopia requests additional or optional information, Infopia marks those as voluntary so that you know it is not required to provide the requested service.
  * Infopia offers you choices regarding how personally identifiable information you provide may be used. You may browse Infopia's website without providing personal information. However, if you want to receive information about Infopia's online products and services, or participate in other online activities (e.g., surveys and contests), Infopia may request that you provide information about yourself.
  * Infopia strives to provide you the opportunity to update or correct the contact information that you have provided to. Infopia has a variety of mechanisms for you to modify and update the contact information that you have provided and is in the process of developing more mechanisms to update your personal data. When you visit the Infopia website, Infopia lets you know in privacy statements how you may currently modify the contact information that you have provided.
  * Infopia protects personally identifiable information. Infopia recognizes industry standards and employs security safeguards to protect personally identifiable information from unauthorized access and misuse. Furthermore, Infopia takes measures to ensure that the information used to process your request is accurate and current.
  * Infopia provides you with a means of contact to learn about information practices and other privacy aspects. Infopia is committed to protecting the privacy of customers and website visitors. 

|  |   
  
---  

---
